<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devAny - A thin client to write codes on iPhone/iPad on devAny</title>
    <link>https://www.devany.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devAny - A thin client to write codes on iPhone/iPad on devAny</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>@shohey1226</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.devany.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Installation on Server The connection of this setup is NOT encrypted. Secure connection is highly recommended. Please follow secure connection after the below instruction is completed.
There are a couple of processes need to run on server to use devAny. In order to avoid this tedious setup, I provide images that includes all required processes and the way to create the image on your end using Packer .
1. Using Docker Docker is well-known container and the easiest way to launch devAny process on server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use terminal</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use-terminal/</guid>
      <description>Terminal is a terminal session to connect to server. You can use screen/tmux to keep sessions in the background because when devAny app is inacitve(open the other app, for example), it cuts the sesesson.
devany command devany command is available and this command opens file or link to Editor and Browser respectively.
 Open file with Editor from Terminal $ devany -f content/how-to-use/index.md  Open link with Browser from Terminal $ devany -l https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use terminal</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/tips/</guid>
      <description> Open file easily Use peco.
# in .bashrc or .bash_profile function pecodaf { devany -f $(find . -type f -o -path ./.git -prune | peco) }  Use deavny command from the history with peco function pecodah { $(history | grep devany | cut -c 8- | peco) }  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use devAny</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use/</guid>
      <description>Desktop Desktop view has terminal, editor and browser. This can be seen by making your device horizontal(landscape).
    Keyboard Command Description     Command + Tab Move window   Command + Tab + Shift Move window - Reverse   Command + / Full screen(back from Full screen)    Setting Setting view is to set up for devAny. This can be seen by making your device vertical(portrait).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use editor</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use-editor/</guid>
      <description>Shortcuts    Keyboard Command Description     Command + s Save file   Command + c Copy   Command + v Paste   Control + Tab Change file   Command + w Close file   Command + n Open new file    There are tons of keybindings on Editor which derives from Ace Editor. It can be set up but may not work some of them as iOS has already uses the keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>web browsing</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/browse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/browse/</guid>
      <description> Open link from Terminal  $ devany -l https://stackoverflow.com  Links  Google Stackoverflow Github Slack Linuxbrew rbenv  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Last updated: Jan 2, 2018
Waza Lab built the devAny app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Waza Lab and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/faq/</guid>
      <description>Q. My terminal is always blank and not responding? A. You need to set up your server. Please go through getting started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use browser</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/how-to-use-browser/</guid>
      <description> Browser is for browsing websites. You can operate with only your keyboard.
 Apple doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow us to go insecure website(http) and only allow secure(SSL/TSL) enabled websites. devAny tries to get insecure websites through server but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work 100%.
How to copy  Find word with command+f Type words and enter to hightlight Type enter to go to the word Type &amp;ldquo;i&amp;rdquo; and use arrow keys + shift to select Command+c to Copy the woreds to clipboard Then you can paste with command+v on terminal, editor or browser   Shortcuts    Keyboard Command Description     Command + i Show hints   Command + c Copy   Command + v Paste   Command + r Reload   Control + p Scroll up   Control + n Scroll down   Command + [ Go back   Command + ] Go forward   Control + Tab Change tab   Command + w Close tab   Command + t Open new tab   Command + + Zoom In   Command + _ Zoom out    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/terms/</guid>
      <description>By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://www.devany.net/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.devany.net/license/</guid>
      <description>devAny software consists of several open source components.
Ace Editor Copyright (c) 2010, Ajax.org B.V. All rights reserved. Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met: * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer. * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>